<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMI</string>
    <!-- Height text view -->
    <string name="textHeight">Height</string>

    <!--weight text view -->
    <string name="textWeight">Weight</string>

    <!--Text calculate -->
    <string name="btnClc">Calculate</string>

    <!--text view Age -->
    <string name="txtAge">Age</string>

    <!-- Hint and CM txt view-->
    <string name="CM">CM</string>

    <!--Hint and CM text view -->
    <string name="KG">KG</string>

    <!-- Hint Edt years -->
    <string name="year">years</string>

    <!--BTN txt Reset  -->
    <string name="btnReset">Reset</string>

    <!--BMI text view -->
    <string name="bmiTxt">BMI</string>

    <!-- -->
    <string name="idlWeight">IDEAL WEIGHT</string>

    <!--Fat text view -->
    <string name="fat">FAT</string>

    <!-- Message text view-->
    <string name="message">message</string>

    <!--guess text view -->
    <string name="guess">?</string>
    <!-- -->
    <string name="inptTpye">numberDecimal</string>

    <!-- -->
    <string name="mesInitial">Enter your details</string>

    <!-- -->
    <string name="height">CM</string>
    <!-- -->
    <string name="actnInfo">Info</string>
    <!-- -->
    <string name="actnExit">Exit</string>
    <!--Home button  view -->
    <string name="BtnHom">Home</string>
    <!-- -->
    <string name="BmiHead">What is BMI?</string>
    <!--Info text -->
    <string name="BmiInfo">The body mass index (BMI), or Quetelet index, is a
                           heuristic proxy for human body fat based on an individual\'s
                           weight and height. BMI does not actually measure the percentage
                           of body fat. It was invented between 1830 and 1850 by the Belgian
                           polymath Adolphe Quetelet during the course of developing \"social
                           physics\". Body mass index is defined as the individual\'s body weight
                           divided by the square of his or her height. The formulae universally
                           used in medicine produce a unit of measure of kg/m2.</string>
    <string name="BmiInfo2">A frequent use of the BMI is to assess how much an individual\'s
        body weight departs from what is normal or desirable for a person of his or her height.
        The weight excess or deficiency may, in part, be accounted for by body fat (adipose tissue)
        although other factors such as muscularity also affect BMI significantly
        (see discussion below and overweight).  The WHO regard a BMI of less than 18.5 as
        underweight and may indicate malnutrition, an eating disorder, or other health problems,
        while a BMI greater than 25 is considered overweight and above 30 is considered obese.
        These ranges of BMI values are valid only as statistical categories when applied to adults,
        and do not predict health.</string>
    <!-- Spinner data -->
    <string-array name="sex">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
